{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820770630","data":{"timestamp":" 946820770629"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" KULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820776349","data":{"timestamp":" 946820776347"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 1ef9a0a0-c0a4-4f76-b4fb-7a0ad33dc6cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" KULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820787298","data":{"timestamp":" 946820787297"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 829d7e57-d8fa-4998-8029-eba289f7029d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_V-J-K"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820791227","data":{"timestamp":" 946820791227"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 829d7e57-d8fa-4998-8029-eba289f7029d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_J-K-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820795446","data":{"timestamp":" 946820795446"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 829d7e57-d8fa-4998-8029-eba289f7029d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_K-V-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820799767","data":{"timestamp":" 946820799766"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 829d7e57-d8fa-4998-8029-eba289f7029d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_D-K-R"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820806015","data":{"timestamp":" 946820806015"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 829d7e57-d8fa-4998-8029-eba289f7029d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_J-Y-K"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820811632","data":{"timestamp":" 946820811632"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 829d7e57-d8fa-4998-8029-eba289f7029d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_V-E-K"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820818477","data":{"timestamp":" 946820818477"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 829d7e57-d8fa-4998-8029-eba289f7029d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_Z-K-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820826967","data":{"timestamp":" 946820826967"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 829d7e57-d8fa-4998-8029-eba289f7029d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_K-I-W"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820834385","data":{"timestamp":" 946820834384"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 829d7e57-d8fa-4998-8029-eba289f7029d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_V-K-F"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820839669","data":{"timestamp":" 946820839669"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 829d7e57-d8fa-4998-8029-eba289f7029d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_O-K-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820845450","data":{"timestamp":" 946820845449"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 829d7e57-d8fa-4998-8029-eba289f7029d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_K_O-K-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820860309","data":{"timestamp":" 946820860309"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 9059e11f-294c-4844-8a55-2f70f177222b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_4-2-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820868011","data":{"timestamp":" 946820868010"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 9059e11f-294c-4844-8a55-2f70f177222b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-1-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820874448","data":{"timestamp":" 946820874448"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 9059e11f-294c-4844-8a55-2f70f177222b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_2-1-3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820882466","data":{"timestamp":" 946820882466"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 9059e11f-294c-4844-8a55-2f70f177222b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-2-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820889313","data":{"timestamp":" 946820889313"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 9059e11f-294c-4844-8a55-2f70f177222b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-2-3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820896093","data":{"timestamp":" 946820896092"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 9059e11f-294c-4844-8a55-2f70f177222b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_1-2-3"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820900910","data":{"timestamp":" 946820900910"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 9059e11f-294c-4844-8a55-2f70f177222b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_1-2-3"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820906438","data":{"timestamp":" 946820906437"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 9059e11f-294c-4844-8a55-2f70f177222b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820911819","data":{"timestamp":" 946820911819"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 9059e11f-294c-4844-8a55-2f70f177222b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-4-1"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820917907","data":{"timestamp":" 946820917907"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 9059e11f-294c-4844-8a55-2f70f177222b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-3"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820922401","data":{"timestamp":" 946820922400"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 9059e11f-294c-4844-8a55-2f70f177222b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-3"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820928703","data":{"timestamp":" 946820928703"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 9059e11f-294c-4844-8a55-2f70f177222b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820933308","data":{"timestamp":" 946820933308"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 9059e11f-294c-4844-8a55-2f70f177222b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820939957","data":{"timestamp":" 946820939957"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 9059e11f-294c-4844-8a55-2f70f177222b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:K..K.all.10.rand.say.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820951915","data":{"timestamp":" 946820951915"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 9059e11f-294c-4844-8a55-2f70f177222b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820957957","data":{"timestamp":" 946820957957"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 9059e11f-294c-4844-8a55-2f70f177222b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820986415","data":{"timestamp":" 946820986414"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 3ecf2916-50e4-40d7-bd2e-2ce4cf519325"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820990706","data":{"timestamp":" 946820990706"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 3ecf2916-50e4-40d7-bd2e-2ce4cf519325"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820994987","data":{"timestamp":" 946820994987"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 3ecf2916-50e4-40d7-bd2e-2ce4cf519325"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946820998713","data":{"timestamp":" 946820998713"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 3ecf2916-50e4-40d7-bd2e-2ce4cf519325"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821002627","data":{"timestamp":" 946821002627"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 3ecf2916-50e4-40d7-bd2e-2ce4cf519325"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821007797","data":{"timestamp":" 946821007797"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 3ecf2916-50e4-40d7-bd2e-2ce4cf519325"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821011890","data":{"timestamp":" 946821011890"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 3ecf2916-50e4-40d7-bd2e-2ce4cf519325"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821015762","data":{"timestamp":" 946821015762"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 3ecf2916-50e4-40d7-bd2e-2ce4cf519325"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821019619","data":{"timestamp":" 946821019619"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 3ecf2916-50e4-40d7-bd2e-2ce4cf519325"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821023755","data":{"timestamp":" 946821023754"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 3ecf2916-50e4-40d7-bd2e-2ce4cf519325"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821028030","data":{"timestamp":" 946821028030"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 3ecf2916-50e4-40d7-bd2e-2ce4cf519325"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821032814","data":{"timestamp":" 946821032813"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 3ecf2916-50e4-40d7-bd2e-2ce4cf519325"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821036942","data":{"timestamp":" 946821036942"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 3ecf2916-50e4-40d7-bd2e-2ce4cf519325"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821038877","data":{"timestamp":" 946821038876"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 3ecf2916-50e4-40d7-bd2e-2ce4cf519325"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821049628","data":{"timestamp":" 946821049628"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 65742e0e-eef7-42ff-83b3-c83693ff6a07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_3-1-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821054696","data":{"timestamp":" 946821054695"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 65742e0e-eef7-42ff-83b3-c83693ff6a07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_1-2-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821061375","data":{"timestamp":" 946821061375"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 65742e0e-eef7-42ff-83b3-c83693ff6a07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-1-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821065965","data":{"timestamp":" 946821065965"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 65742e0e-eef7-42ff-83b3-c83693ff6a07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-1-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821070621","data":{"timestamp":" 946821070621"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 65742e0e-eef7-42ff-83b3-c83693ff6a07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-1-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821077377","data":{"timestamp":" 946821077377"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 65742e0e-eef7-42ff-83b3-c83693ff6a07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_2-1-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821082028","data":{"timestamp":" 946821082028"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 65742e0e-eef7-42ff-83b3-c83693ff6a07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_2-1-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821088836","data":{"timestamp":" 946821088836"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 65742e0e-eef7-42ff-83b3-c83693ff6a07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-1-4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821092785","data":{"timestamp":" 946821092784"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" 65742e0e-eef7-42ff-83b3-c83693ff6a07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-1-4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821117317","data":{"timestamp":" 946821117317"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821118368","data":{"timestamp":" 946821118368"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821120926","data":{"timestamp":" 946821120926"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821122709","data":{"timestamp":" 946821122709"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821125322","data":{"timestamp":" 946821125321"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821126368","data":{"timestamp":" 946821126368"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821129020","data":{"timestamp":" 946821129020"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821130800","data":{"timestamp":" 946821130800"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821133075","data":{"timestamp":" 946821133075"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821134114","data":{"timestamp":" 946821134113"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821136694","data":{"timestamp":" 946821136694"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821136905","data":{"timestamp":" 946821136905"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821137798","data":{"timestamp":" 946821137798"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821140207","data":{"timestamp":" 946821140207"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821142724","data":{"timestamp":" 946821142724"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821144372","data":{"timestamp":" 946821144372"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821146984","data":{"timestamp":" 946821146984"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821148021","data":{"timestamp":" 946821148021"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821151178","data":{"timestamp":" 946821151178"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821152224","data":{"timestamp":" 946821152224"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821155035","data":{"timestamp":" 946821155035"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821156072","data":{"timestamp":" 946821156072"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821158989","data":{"timestamp":" 946821158989"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821159311","data":{"timestamp":" 946821159311"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821160112","data":{"timestamp":" 946821160112"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821162743","data":{"timestamp":" 946821162743"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821165423","data":{"timestamp":" 946821165422"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821165630","data":{"timestamp":" 946821165630"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821166532","data":{"timestamp":" 946821166532"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821168923","data":{"timestamp":" 946821168923"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821171585","data":{"timestamp":" 946821171585"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821172622","data":{"timestamp":" 946821172622"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821175577","data":{"timestamp":" 946821175577"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821176031","data":{"timestamp":" 946821176031"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821176716","data":{"timestamp":" 946821176716"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821179153","data":{"timestamp":" 946821179153"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821181880","data":{"timestamp":" 946821181880"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821183517","data":{"timestamp":" 946821183517"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821186352","data":{"timestamp":" 946821186352"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821187392","data":{"timestamp":" 946821187392"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821190104","data":{"timestamp":" 946821190104"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821191153","data":{"timestamp":" 946821191153"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821193822","data":{"timestamp":" 946821193821"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821194864","data":{"timestamp":" 946821194864"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821197550","data":{"timestamp":" 946821197550"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821197757","data":{"timestamp":" 946821197757"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821198754","data":{"timestamp":" 946821198754"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821201166","data":{"timestamp":" 946821201166"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821204508","data":{"timestamp":" 946821204508"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821204586","data":{"timestamp":" 946821204586"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821221523","data":{"timestamp":" 946821221523"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821230331","data":{"timestamp":" 946821230330"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821241209","data":{"timestamp":" 946821241208"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" f19cb372-5df1-479b-9879-252cc44697f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821253108","data":{"timestamp":" 946821253108"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" c0491db1-b190-4613-9d45-cbab26d1662b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LAMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAMBA"," userResponse":" LAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821261029","data":{"timestamp":" 946821261029"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" c0491db1-b190-4613-9d45-cbab26d1662b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LAMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821262596","data":{"timestamp":" 946821262596"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" c0491db1-b190-4613-9d45-cbab26d1662b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LAINI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAINI"," userResponse":" LAINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821266423","data":{"timestamp":" 946821266423"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" c0491db1-b190-4613-9d45-cbab26d1662b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LAINI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821267994","data":{"timestamp":" 946821267994"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" c0491db1-b190-4613-9d45-cbab26d1662b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LALA"," userResponse":" LALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821271587","data":{"timestamp":" 946821271586"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" c0491db1-b190-4613-9d45-cbab26d1662b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821273148","data":{"timestamp":" 946821273148"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" c0491db1-b190-4613-9d45-cbab26d1662b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMA"," userResponse":" LIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821276500","data":{"timestamp":" 946821276500"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" c0491db1-b190-4613-9d45-cbab26d1662b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821278057","data":{"timestamp":" 946821278057"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" c0491db1-b190-4613-9d45-cbab26d1662b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LIMAU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMAU"," userResponse":" LIMAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821281676","data":{"timestamp":" 946821281676"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" c0491db1-b190-4613-9d45-cbab26d1662b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LIMAU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMAU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821283231","data":{"timestamp":" 946821283231"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" c0491db1-b190-4613-9d45-cbab26d1662b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LORI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821286681","data":{"timestamp":" 946821286681"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" c0491db1-b190-4613-9d45-cbab26d1662b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LORI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821288708","data":{"timestamp":" 946821288708"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" c0491db1-b190-4613-9d45-cbab26d1662b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" LORI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946821288886","data":{"timestamp":" 946821288886"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_164601"," gameId":" c0491db1-b190-4613-9d45-cbab26d1662b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LORI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}